You're making a big deal.
Sorry. You know, whatever.
Psh. It's all good.
(Penny:)Anyway, that's it.
I just thought you should know.
(Leonard:)Am I allowed to ask
how the class is going?
It's good. We've been talking
about the origins of slavery.
- I turn in my first paper tomorrow.
- I can help with that.
There's lots of perspectives to take.
Economic, sociological, political...
(Penny:)Hey, this is my paper.
(Penny:)And my perspective
is that slavery is bad.
(Penny:)And my professor's black,
so I'm pretty sure that's the right answer.
- Can I take a look?
- No, Leonard. This is my thing.
- Okay. I get it.
- Thank you.
(Leonard:)It's like when I started doing chin-ups.
(Leonard:)I didn't want you to see
until I could do one.
(Leonard:)FYI, really close.
(Penny:)Thank you. Now, behave yourself
and eat your dinner.
And if you're lucky,
you get to sleep with a college girl.
Really? I went to four years of college
and five years of grad school.